Contact

+6285156263732 (Mobile) hello.reyhanfirnas@gmail.co m

www.linkedin.com/in/reyhanfirnas (LinkedIn)

firnasreyhan.github.io/ (Portfolio)

Top Skills

Kotlin

Android Studio

Android Development

Languages

English (Elementary)

Javanese (Native or Bilingual)

Indonesian (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

Belajar Membuat Aplikasi Android untuk Pemula

Ethical Hacking Fundamentals

Muhammad Reyhan Firnas Adani

Android Developer

Kepanjen, East Java, Indonesia

Summary

I am a programmer with at least three years of experience with a focus on Android Developer. I am interested in learning new technologies of Mobile Development.

The first two years of my experience as a freelance Android Developer in several large companies in Indonesia, one of which was PT United Tractors Tbk and the last year of my experience as a full time remote Android Developer at PT. Gramedia Asri Media. As an Android Developer I am familiar with Kotlin, Java, Retrofit, Room, Coroutines, SQLite, and MVVM Design Pattern, Firebase. And now I'm working for PT. Sekar Laut, Tbk. in the development of monitoring sales applications.

Experience

PT. Sekar Laut, Tbk.
Android Developer
November 2022 - April 2023 (6 months)
Surabaya, East Java, Indonesia

- 1. Create an application that has the function to submit and validate forms using an android smartphone.
- 2. Responsible for making applications based on the designs that have been provided.
- 3. Responsible for implementing features that have been discussed with the Project Managers.

KOMPAS GRAMEDIA

Android Developer October 2021 - October 2022 (1 year 1 month) Jakarta, Indonesia

- 1. Responsible for making applications based on the design provided.
- 2. Responsible for correcting errors on application.

- 3. Responsible for implementing features discussed with Project Manager and System Analyst.
- 4. Responsible for publishing apps on the Google Play Store.

PT United Tractors Tbk

Android Developer

January 2021 - September 2021 (9 months)

Jakarta, Indonesia

- 1. Create an application that has the function to submit and validate forms using an android smartphone.
- 2. Responsible for making applications based on the designs that have been provided.
- 3. Responsible for implementing features that have been discussed with the Project

Managers.

Institut Ilmu Kesehatan STRADA Indonesia

Android Developer

December 2020 - January 2021 (2 months)

Kediri, East Java, Indonesia

- 1. Create an application that has a function to perform early detection of breast cancer by filling out a questionnaire using android smartphones.
- 2. Responsible for making applications based on the designs that have been provided.
- 3. Responsible for implementing features that have been discussed with the Project Managers.

STIKI Malang

1 year 7 months

Academic Assistant

September 2019 - September 2020 (1 year 1 month)

Malang, East Java, Indonesia

- 1. Analyze hardware and software requirements for practical activities.
- 2. Arrange changes to the practicum module.
- 3. Assist with the practicum process.
- 4. Coordinate laboratory assistants.
- 5. Assist in preparing workshop activities.

Practice Assistant

March 2019 - August 2019 (6 months)

Malang, East Java, Indonesia

1. Guiding practicum activities

PT Perkebunan Nusantara X

Android Developer

September 2019 - March 2020 (7 months)

Surabaya, East Java, Indonesia

- 1. Create an official news portal application for PT Perkebunan Nusantara X using an android smartphone.
- 2. Responsible for making applications based on the designs that have been provided.
- 3. Responsible for implementing features that have been discussed with the Project Manager.
- 4. Responsible for publishing applications on the Google Play Store.

Digiponic

Android Developer

May 2019 - October 2019 (6 months)

Malang, East Java, Indonesia

- 1. Help improve the vegetable ordering application using an android smartphone.
- 2. Help improve the point of sale application for auto repair shops using a smartphone android.

PT. Universal Big Data

Android Developer

January 2016 - December 2016 (1 year)

Malang, East Java, Indonesia

- 1. Help develop the BTN Properti application.
- 2. Responsible for making applications based on UI / UX.
- 3. Responsible for fixing bugs.

Education

STIKI Malang

Bachelor's degree, Informatics · (2017 - 2021)

SMK Negeri 4 Malang

High School Diploma, Computer Software Engineering · (2014 - 2017)